That has
happened
Om Om
[Music]
Do it
Hello friends, the pen stand
I am going to tell you about is our
layer who called us from Rajkot, Gujarat.
He had
taken an insurance policy from some company, whose actual
statement was above 90% on 26 March
2019. We had taken this polythene and its
Maya in the center in 2020. After almost a year and a quarter,
this Maya of oil. This question was that he was
working at a construction site. While working there, he met with a
road accident, for which
he spent Rs 2 lakh for treatment, the
bill of which he also paid from his pocket
because the company rejected his cream after seeing it.
After that, when he had a tumor on his return,
Shukla 15 or so, the company
rejected the medical reimbursement and refused
injections. You can see the letter on your screen.
In this letter, it is
written that what is your brother, the
waiting period for it is two years. I was
very surprised to know that
in an accidental case, there is a road getting error and a
seat.
Well, whatever the root of the wedding  It
comes under specific diseases like knee replacement or
leg amputation, the
waiting period for all these is this and it was
also clearly written in the policy body of the company, the worst thing is that
friends, the agent for which they had taken the policy had
referred them for
half a day, he had already
told the customer that the result was there and should this
centre really have been the result but when their public
representatives and
their Baba called they did not provide any such services, they
even stopped picking up the phone, now I will ask you how was
your experience with this company,
Rao Kanwar Singh, she said that
after my accident, my experience was very
bad that I had to call the customer care, but I could
not find any solution for you,
then being upset, I sent mails to the corporation,
which the company also did not like to reply to, I had to
spend 15 days, the reaction of the accident that happened to them, the
reforms
and which I got, if you want to take services from us, then it has happened
with us, so that
we all would know that
our country  That 130 crore people do not understand enough about
what is in the policy. If we
talk about one of the top companies on this matter, then
please there are many companies but when it comes to
something like this, people are not able to file a complaint on time
or else they go away. That is why you have taken a
health insurance policy only on the basis of that royal notification
because the
role of the policy provider is the biggest. If
you do not subscribe, then you
may face a big problem at the time of taking the policy. If he is not helping you then
he will not help you in future also
like he did not help Sachin, that
I am adding now, so this is a place
where you do not face any problem and you
get time, then if you take it then they
talk completely about covering all kinds of diseases like subscription till the pimp.
Despite this, the company has
won these, so you can understand
how important it is for you people that
who will stand with you at the time of claim. Now
this is the subject that regarding them, they are asking for help from us
and they do not have it, still
we are giving it to them, telling them, making them
wait that  Yes, you should have got this claim,
type it now, but the
amount of trouble they have taken away from you during this time is
priceless, so if
this has happened to you because of this, then please share it with me
so that we can help you with new serials
and together we will make people aware,
friends, if you found this video
useful, then please subscribe to my channel,
please like my video
and press the bell icon
so that you will keep getting the latest updates regarding Mirch videos,
it's time for watching my video
[Music]